Contact

kernelpanicj0sh@protonmail.

www.linkedin.com/in/ kernelpanicj0sh (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

IT Hardware Support
IT Outsourcing
Information Technology

Languages

English

Certifications

City & Guilds Level 3 IT Professional

Josh Stubbs

Frontend Developer

Darlington

Summary

I have over 6 years experience within the IT industry, starting as an IT apprentice before working with several companies in providing end user support as well as server administration and maintenance.

During this time I have always had a great interest in coding with different languages and realised that I have a true passion for turning ideas into reality and being able to do that from a blank text editor I find very rewarding and exciting.

I am currently training to become a Frontend developer via Codecademy, once I have completed this course and finished my projects I will then progress to the full stack course to further progress my knowledge and apply my skills to more in-depth and complicated projects.

I have always enjoyed problem solving and have become very competent in finding the correct information I need using online resources.

During my training period I have also taken up several design courses focusing on 2D pixel and vector art, I believe this is a very important skill when it comes to designing websites and allows me to have more involvement in the overall finished look of a website/application.

Experience

kernelpanicj0sh.github.io Frontend Developer December 2020 - Present (2 months)

Training to become a Frontend Developer via Codecademy specialising in html5, css3, javascript, sql & php.

Using frameworks such as React & node.js hosting via Apache2 & Microsoft Azure.

I am also learning to create 2D pixel Art & Vector Art for Web Design.

Aspire Technology Solutions
Quickfix IT Analyst
October 2019 - November 2020 (1 year 2 months)
Heworth, Gateshead

technocopy IT Support Analyst September 2017 - October 2019 (2 years 2 months) Darlington, United Kingdom

Atos

IT Support Analyst October 2016 - September 2017 (1 year)

Baltic Training Services
IT Support Apprentice
July 2014 - August 2016 (2 years 2 months)

Education

Carmel RC College · (2007 - 2012)